We're running low on resumes.
이제 이력서가
다 떨어져 간다
You want a job
with Popular Mechanics?
정말 파퓰러 정비사에서
일하고 싶어?
정비사라면, 거기서
너부터 정비하느라 힘들겠다
If you're gonna work for mechanics,
those are the ones.
Guys, I'm going for anything here.
I can't be a waitress anymore.
얘들아! 난 어디든 갈 거야
더 이상 웨이트리스는 싫어
I'm sick of the lousy tips.
I'm sick of being called "Excuse Me."
쥐꼬리만한 팁도 지겹고
'여기요! '하고 부르는 것도 끔찍해
종이에 비었어
-Paper cut! Paper cut!
-Here.
이거라도 마셔
Grapefruit juice! Grapefruit juice!
포도주스를 줘야지
이제 거의 다했고
20개 정도 남았어
Okay, we're almost done.
Only 20 more to go.
이거 수정 좀 하자
-Rach, did you proofread these?
-Yeah. Why?
그래, 뭔데?
Nothing. I'm sure they'll be
impressed with your "compuper" skills.
'컴퓨러'를 잘 한다는 말을
믿어줄까 싶어서!
세상에!
전부 이랬을 거 아냐!
Oh, my God!
Do you think it's on all of them?
No, I'm sure the Xerox machine
caught a few.
괜찮아
가끔 복사기도 실수를 해
The One With the Poker
They call this a love seat but I'm not
feeling anything special towards you.
소파를 연인들의 자리라는데
너한테는 아무 감정도 안 생겨
나 왔어
-Hey, guys.
-Hey.
- 안녕
어서 오세요!
뭐 드릴까요?
Hi, ladies.
Can I get you anything?
Did you bring the mail?
답신 왔니?
- 아주 많아
- 그래?
-Lots of responses.
-Really? Sure, we have scones left!
물론 케이크 있지!
Read them.
어서 읽어봐
"Dear Miss Greene:
Thank you for your inquiry. However"
그린 양, 지원해주셔서
감사합니다만...!
- 사과 케이크도 있어
- 그린 양
-We have apple cinnamon
-"Dear Ms. Greene...." Yeah, yeah! No.
네, 네, 네
됐다!
- 와!
- 뭐야?
-What?
-Your Visa bill is huge!
카드 값 엄청나다!
Give me that.
이리 내놔
Linda's great.
Why won't you go out with her?
너 정말 왜 그래?
린다 괜찮잖아
다시 만나보지 그래?
모르겠어
-I don't know.
-ls this about her...
만화 주인공처럼
마법이라도 일어나길 바래?
... "The Flintstones could
have really happened" thing?
It's not just that. I want someone
who does something for me...
그런 게 아냐
그저 누군가, 누군가...
내 가슴을 뛰게 할 사람!
그런 사람이...
...who gets my heart pounding.
Who makes me....
Little playthings with yarn?
앞치마 두른 여자는?
뭐?
What?
Could you want her more?
쟤가 더 좋아?
Who?
누구?
Dee, the sarcastic sister
from What's Happening!!.
한번 꼬아서 말해주랴?
대체 뭔 일이야?
Look, I'm totally over her.
난 정말로 정리했어
- 난... 안녕
- 안녕! 커피?
-Hi!
-Coffee?
- 아니, 우린 됐어
- 그래
-No, we're fine.
-Okay.
닥쳐!
-Shut up!
-We're not saying anything.
아무 말도 안 했어
-What?
-Joey cried last night.
뭔데?
어젯밤에 조이가 울었어
고맙다
-Thank you.
-We were playing poker
포커를 쳤거든
There was chocolate on the three.
It looked like an eight.
3자에 초콜릿이 묻어서
8자로 보였어, 됐냐?
그 꼴을 봤어야하는데
보았노라, 울었노라!
You should have seen him.
"Read them and weep!"
And then he did.
진짜 그랬어
Now, how come you guys
have never played poker with us?
왜 우리랑은 포커를 안 쳐?
왜 그런 거야?
남자만의 게임이야?
Yeah, what is that?
Like some kind of sexist guy thing?
섹시한 남자의 전형이니?
포커는 남자만 하는 거야?
-It's poker, so only guys can play?
-No. Women can play.
아냐, 여자도 할 수 있어
Then, what is it? Some kind of, like,
some kind of, you know
그럼 왜들 그래?
그럼, 그게, 그게...
이유가 뭐야?
All right, what is it?
여자들이 안 끼는 것 뿐이야
There are just no women
in our game.
맞아! 포커 칠 줄 아는
여자도 본 적이 없어
We just don't know any
women who know how to play poker.
- 웃겨!
- 어머...
그것도 변명이야?
아주 전형적인 남자들의 답이군
That is a lame excuse.
It's a typical guy response.
그럼 너희들 포커 칠 줄 알아?
Do you know how to play?
아니!
No.
가르쳐주면 되잖아!
-But you could teach us.
-No.
싫어!
이제 카드를 뽑아
Okay, so now we draw cards.
So I wouldn't need any.
I have a straight.
난 필요 없지?
스트레이트를 들고 있거든
- 잘한다
- 축하해
-Oh, good for you!
-Congratulations!
-Pheebs, how many do you want?
-I just need two.
피비, 넌 뭐가 필요해?
두 장, 스페이드 10과
클로버 6
The 10 of spades and the 6 of clubs.
-No, you can't
-I have the 10 of spades! Here.
- 안돼, 그러면 안돼...
- 나한테 스페이드 10있어
- 내가 줄게
- 고마워
Thanks!
안돼, 이렇게 하면 안돼
-No, you can't do that.
-Don't need them. I'm going for fours.
아냐, 괜찮아
난 필요 없어
- 난 4로 맞출 거야
- 그래
Oh, you're
너는...
You're going for fours.
Chandler, could you? Thanks, man.
- 챈들러?
- 응
Here we go.
먹으면서 해!
연어와 과일이야
We've got salmon roulettes
and crudites.
What are you doing?
모니카, 뭐하는 거야?
이건 포커 게임이야
In poker, there's no food
with more than one syllable.
한 음절 이상 되는
음식은 내놓지마
칩, 딥, 프렛츠...
It's got to be like chips
or dip or pretz
I hope you'll let it slide just
this once. I was all out of "pretz."
이번만 넘어가
프렛츠는 다 떨어졌어
Now the dealer
- 이 시점에서 딜러는...
- 됐어, 다 알아
We got it. Let's play for real.
High stakes. Big bucks!
- 진짜 게임을 하자
- 그래 해!
돈 걸고 하자구!
진짜 하고 싶어?
You sure? Phoebe just threw away two
jacks because they didn't look happy.
피비는 잭을 두 장이나 버렸어
찡그린 얼굴은 싫대
난 준비됐어, 걸어봐!
But I'm ready. So just deal.
여러분, 마지막 수업!
Okay, last-minute lesson!
Joey....
조이, 3, 8!
8! 3!
Three.
Eight.
Eight. Three.
All right, very good.
젠장, 젠장!
Damn it, damn it, damn it!
봤지?
조이가 5가 두 장이었어
Joey had two fives showing,
so for you to raise was
- 그럼 네가 올리려면...
- 그래서?
Yes?
배짱을 튕겨야지
Downright gutsy.
-I see, so you were lying.
-About what?
이제 알겠어
거짓말이었지?
- 무슨?
- 패가 좋단 걸 숨긴 거?
-About how good your cards were.
-I was bluffing.
그걸 뻥카라고 해
뻥카가 뭐야?
And what is bluffing?
거짓말의 다른 표현이야?
Is it not another word for lying?
Sorry to break up this party, but I've
got to go fax resumes before work.
판을 깨서 미안하지만
가서 이력서를 써야돼
레이첼, 이제 때가 왔어
-We've got to settle.
-Settle what?
무슨 때?
버지니아의
제임스타운 식민지!
The Jamestown colony of Virginia.
See, King George is giving us
the land....
조지 왕이 그 땅을 준대
게임하자구, 게임!
우리한테 돈도 꿨잖아
-The game, Rachel. You owe us money.
-Right.
알았어
It's their first time.
Let's forget about the money.
얘들은 처음이잖아
돈은 걸지 말고 쳐
- 싫어
- 안돼, 돈 낼 거야
Hell, no. We'll pay!
난 벌써 답을 찾았어
Monica, I had another
answer all ready.
그렇지?
한판 더하자
And you know what?
We want a rematch.
난 좋아, 돈만 낸다면
That's fine with me.
Could use some money.
되게 재밌나보네?
-You're enjoying this, aren't you?
-Well, yeah, I am.
응... 그래
친구들 돈만 우려낸다면
뭐든 좋구나!
So you get your ya-yas
by taking money from your friends.
- 그래
- 나도 뭐든 좋다고 봐!
Yes, and I get my ya-yas from KEA.
You have to put them together
yourself, but they cost less.
너희들도 좋다고 생각하면
돈이 안 아까워질 거야
레이첼, 이건 포커야!
이기기 위한 게임이지
Look, this is poker.
I play to win.
내가 이기기 위해서는
다른 사람이 져야돼
For me to win,
others have to lose.
그러니까 나랑 포커를 할 땐
우정을 기대하지마
If you're gonna play,
don't expect me to be nice.
Because once those cards are dealt....
일단 카드가 돌고 나면...
그래서?
Yeah?
I'm not a nice guy.
피도 눈물도 없다
All right, let's eat.
얘들아, 먹자!
거기서 주문한 거니?
'사랑하는 레이첼 피자집'
Did you get that
from the "I Love Rachel Pizzeria"?
-You still on that?
-What was with that Black Bart speech?
아직도 그 얘기야?
도대체 그 따위 연설은
왜 한 거야?
"When I play poker,
I'm not a nice guy."
"포커 칠 때는,
피도 눈물도 없다"
You're way off.
과장하지마
나도 동감이야, 로스
넌 레이첼을 사랑해
No, I don't think so,
because I think you love her!
아냐! 한때는 그런 감정도
있었지만 이젠 아냐
No. I might have had feelings
for her at one time. Not anymore.
I just
난 이제... 마르셀!
Marcel! Where are you going
with that disk?
그 CD는 뭐하게?
제자리에 갖다 놔
You are not putting that on again.
마르셀! 버튼 누르면
넌 오늘 끝장난다
If you press that button,
you are in very big trouble.
로스의 그런 태도가 믿어져?
You believe what a jerk
Ross was being?
난 알아
오빠는 지는 걸 싫어해
-Yeah, I know.
-He can get really competitive.
왜?
What?
"Hello, kettle? This is Monica.
You're black!"
"안녕, 까마귀?
모니카야, 너도 까매"
Please!
제발...
I'm not as bad as Ross.
난 오빠만큼은 아냐
정말 달라?
그림 퀴즈 사건은?
I beg to differ.
The Pictionary incident?
That wasn't an incident.
그게 무슨 사건이야!
낱말 설명하다가...
손이 미끄러워서 접시가 깨졌지
I was gesturing and the plate
slipped out of my hand.
면접에 오래!
-I got an interview!
-You're kidding! Where?
- 정말?
- 면접에 오래!
어디?
색스 5번 가!
Saks Fifth Avenue.
레이첼...
Oh, Rachel!
엄마가 집으로 오라고
손짓하는 기분이다
It's like the mother ship
is calling you home.
무슨 일인데?
-What's the job?
-Assistant buyer.
구매 보조야!
I would be shopping!
쇼핑이라면 좋지!
일이야!
For a living!
That's Aunt lris. She's been
playing poker since she was 5.
오셨다
아이리스 숙모는 5살 때부터
포커를 치신 분이야
You've got to listen
to every word she says.
한마디도 빼먹지 말고 들어
어서 오세요!
토니 랜달이 죽었니?
-ls Tony Randall dead?
-I don't think so.
- 아뇨, 왜요?
- 아닐 거예요
지금쯤은 죽었을 게야
내 차로 박았거든
-He may be now. I hit him with my car.
-My God, really?
- 어머!
- 정말이요?
아니, 뻥카야!
수업 제 1장!
No, that's bluffing.
Lesson number one.
잘 들어라
포커판의 대화는 모두 뻥이다!
Let me tell you something. Everything
you hear at a poker game is pure crap!
- 귀걸이 예쁘다
- 감사합니다
-Nice earrings.
-Thank you.
-Girls, sit down.
-Aunt lris, this is Phoebe and Rachel.
아가씨들, 앉지
숙모, 여긴 피비고
얘는 레이첼...
그래, 주차비 올라간다
어서 하자!
Listen, I'm parked at a meter.
Let's do it. Okay?
우선 5장 게임을 하고
하이-로우 게임을 배우고
We'll start with five-card draw.
Then we'll go into the studs and the
hold 'ems. I talked to Cousin Nathan.
네이선한테 전화 왔었다
카드 패는 미리 보지마!
Don't touch the cards
when somebody is dealing.
How is Nathan?
- 네이선은 잘 지내죠?
- 늘 똑같지
Now he thinks he's a man
in a woman's body.
여자한테 꽉 잡혀
힘들어죽겠대
남자 때문에 여자가 힘든 건
아니구요?
Don't you mean
a woman in a man's body?
It should be so simple.
말처럼 쉬우면 좋지!
제발, 다른 노래 좀 듣자
Ross, could we please listen
to anything else?
알았어
All right.
이따가 밤새 틀어주마
I'm gonna pay for that tonight.
- 안녕
Hi. Guys, guess what?
얘들아, 어떻게 됐게?
The fifth dentist caved, and now
they're all recommending Trident?
5번 가 치과에서 포기하고
삼지창 들고 덤비대?
No, the interview!
아니, 면접!
Unbelievable!
She absolutely loved me.
면접관이 진짜로
날 맘에 들어했어
We talked for over two hours.
We've the same taste in clothes.
거의 두 시간 반 동안
대화를 했는데...
옷에 관한 취향도 같고
그 여자 사촌도 아는 사람이야
And I went to camp with her cousin.
그 일은 나한테 딱이야!
난 할 수 있어!
-The job is perfect! I can do this.
-That's great!
- 잘됐다, 레이첼
- 축하해
- 재미난 얘기도 들었어
- 좋아, 레이첼!
-Then she told a funny story.
-Great, tell us and we'll laugh.
어서 우리를 웃겨 줘
빨리 포커 해야지
Let's play poker!
Listen, we talked about it and
if you don't wanna play, it's okay.
얘들아, 아까 얘기한 건데
너희들은 억지로 할 필요 없어
그래! 다른 게임도 괜찮아
Yes, we can play some other game.
Like Pictionary?
그림 퀴즈 어때?
아주 좋아
그래도 포커 치고 싶어
Very funny.
-But we'd like to try poker again.
-Yes, I think we should.
- 어때, 숙녀분들?
- 당연히 좋지
-Do you want me to shuffle those?
-That's okay, I'm gonna give it a go.
내가 카드 섞어줄까?
아니, 괜찮아
내가 한번 해볼게
- 좋아
So Pheebs owes $7. 50.
Monica owes $10.00.
피비는 7달러 50센트
모니카는 10달러
레이첼은
15달러나 빚이다!
And Rachel, you owe 1 5 big ones!
Thanks for teaching us Cross-Eyed
Mary. We gotta play that other way.
너희들한테 많은 걸 배웠다
다른 게임을 배우는 게 좋을 거야
7달러 50센트 여깄어
근데 이 돈은 저주받은 거야
All right, here's my $7.50.
But this money is cursed.
- 뭐?
- 주문을 걸었어!
-What?
-I cursed it!
Now bad things will happen
to the spender.
이 돈 쓰는 사람은
재수 없는 일만 당할 거야
I'll take it.
Bad things happen to me anyway.
괜찮아, 난 어차피
재수가 없는 놈이니까
This way, I can split them up
with a movie.
이걸로 영화나 보면서
재수나 깨볼게
이제 포커의 여신
레이첼의 15달러만 남았군
So that just leaves the big Greene
poker machine, who owes 1 5.
Could you be any smugger?
좀 깎아줄 수 없어?
글쎄...
Let's see. Rach, I'm opening up
a new art gallery...
내가 미술관을 새로 열면
초상을 걸 거야
...and I could sure use the portraits
of Lincoln and Hamilton.
링컨과 해밀턴
아주 사내답다
It's so typical.
"I'm a man! I have a penis!
"난 남자야! 싸나이라구!"
"여자한테 힘을 발휘하려면
돈이 있어야 돼"
I have to win money
to exert my power over women!"
오늘이 끝이 아냐
또 다시 할거야
This isn't over.
We'll play you again.
We'll win. You'll lose.
그땐 우리가 이기고
너희가 질 거야
너희가 빌고 우린 웃지
You'll beg. We'll laugh.
We'll take every last dime you have.
And you'll hate yourselves forever!
그때, 돈을 탈탈 털리고
징징 울어봐라!
그거 꼭 우리 심정 같지 않니?
Kind of stepped on
my point there, Mon.
어떻게 그럴 수 있냐?
얼마나 잃었어?
I can't believe you lost!
How much did they take?
- 몰라요, 한 30달러쯤
- 맞아요
Like 30 bucks.
너희가 잃은 돈을
내가 다 따주마
-I'll give you that money back.
-Really?
정말요?
아니, 뻥이야!
아직 기본도 모르냐?
No, I'm bluffing!
You guys haven't learned crap!
카드 줘봐
-Hand me the cards!
-Can l?
- 만져도 돼요?
- 그래
Yes!
미리 돈을 주고 치지 그래?
Wanna give us your money now? We can
skip the formality of really playing.
어차피 줄 돈인데
나중에 주면 속 쓰리잖아
No, that's fine. We'll see who has
the last laugh, monkey boy.
아니, 괜찮아
최후에 웃는 자가 누군지 봐
원숭이 아저씨!
Done with chitchat?
Ready for serious poker?
말씨름들 끝났으면
본격적으로 치는 거 어때?
애꾸눈 잭이 자꾸 붙네!
You guys, look! The one-eyed jack
follows me wherever I go.
알았어, 진지하게!
Right. Serious poker.
오늘은 연어 준비 안 했어?
-Mon, got any more of those salmon?
-You want to eat or play poker?
연어 먹을래?
포커 할래?
잠깐, 어디 가?
-Where are you going?
-To the bathroom.
화장실에
Want to go to the bathroom
or play poker?
화장실 갈래, 포커 칠래?
화장실 갈래
Go to the bathroom.
- 난 피자 주문할게
- 안돼, 안돼!
-Well, I'm gonna order a pizza.
-No!
I'm waiting to hear from that job.
The store closes at 9:00. Eat then.
면접 결과 기다리는 중이야
회사가 9시에 끝나니까 그때 해
알았다, 배고픔을 이겨주는
부스러기나 먹지
That's fine. I'll just have a Tic Tac
to hold me over.
좋아, 신시내티 게임!
속이기 없기, 돈 걸어
All right. Cincinnati. No blinds.
Everybody, ante.
Yes!
좋다!
Or no.
아니, 나빠!
좋아!
네 돈은 내 거야, 그린 양!
-All right! Your money's mine, Greene.
-Your fly's open, Geller.
남대문이나 닫게, 겔러 군!
You know what I just realized?
Joker is poker with a "J"!
지금 막 깨달은 게 뭐게?
조커와 포커가 비슷해
우연일까?
Coincidence?
That's jo-incidence with a "C"!
악연도 우연이고
필연도 우연이다
-Phoebe?
-Yeah, I'm out.
피비? 피비...
난 빠질래!
- 난 들어가
- 나도
-I'm in.
-Me too.
나도! 넌 뭐야?
Me too.
What do you got?
You better hop out of the shower,
because I got a flush.
플래쉬 터뜨릴 준비해
난 플러쉬야
어이, 물러서, 젊은이!
난 6이 넷이야!
Well, well, well!
Hop back in, bucko,
because I got four sixes!
내가 이겼다
진짜로 이겼어!
I got four sixes! I won!
I actually won! Oh, my God!
어머, 세상에!
You know what?
I'll make a little Ross pile.
로스를 위해 산을 쌓을 거야
이거 로스 거지? 이것도?
Look!
I think that one was Ross'.
And I think that one was Ross'.
이게 네 돈이다
다신 구경도 못해
Well, I have got your money
And you'll never see it
And your fly's still open
아직도 남대문은 열렸네
I made you look
나한테 인사했지?
-I'm in.
-I couldn't be in-er.
난 들어가!
배짱이다
Monica, in or out?
모니카?
들어가? 빠져?
이 게임 싫어!
I hate this game!
조이, 네 차례야
Joey, your bet.
I fold like a hooker
who got hit in the stomach...
난 접을래, 미친 뚱뚱보한테
얻어맞은 창녀처럼 기운 빠지네
... by a fat guy
with sores on his face.
I'm out.
빠진단 소리야!
로스?
-Ross?
-I'm very in.
당연히 들어가
챈들러?
-Chandler?
-Couldn't be more out.
이번엔 빠질래
나도! 레이첼?
Me too. Rachel?
네 거 받고, 올려볼까?
I will see you and I'll raise you.
Do you wanna waste another buck?
어때? 계속 따라올래?
No, not this time.
What did you have?
아니, 이번엔 안 해
- 뭐였니?
- 말 안 해
-I'm not telling.
-Show them.
- 그러지 말고...
- 싫어
-No.
-Show them!
- 끝났잖아
- 손 치워, 싫어!
-Get your hands out of there!
-I've had dates like this.
저런 여자랑
데이트 한 적 있지
Boy, you really can't stand
to lose, can you?
지는 거 못 참겠지?
Your whole face is getting red.
Veins popping out of your temple!
얼굴이 빨개졌어
핏줄들이 터지기 직전이야
Plus, that shirt doesn't really
match those pants.
게다가 셔츠와 바지가
정말 안 어울려
-I'm not losing.
-You're definitely losing.
난 지지 않아
- 진다는 말은 하지마...
- 많이 잃었어
여보세요, 레이첼입니다
Hello. Rachel Greene.
잠시만요
그 회사야
Excuse me. It's about the job!
Barbara, hi! How are you?
바바라, 안녕하세요?
아뇨, 이해해요
No, I understand.
네, 그럼요
아뇨, 괜찮아요
Come on. No, I'm fine.
Don't be silly. Yeah.
그럴 것 없어요
근데 혹시 다른 매장엔...
여보세요? 여보세요?
But if anything else
opens up, please
Hello?
유감이다
Sorry, Rach.
- 일터는 얼마든지 있어
- 그래, 알아
There's gonna be lots
of other stuff.
Okay.
Where were we?
어디까지 했지?
5장으로 하는 거
Five-card draw. Jacks are better.
Nothing wild. Everybody, ante.
잭이 낫지, 모두 돈들 걸어
-Look, Rach, we don't have to do this.
-Yes, we do.
레이첼, 우리 그만 하자
그냥 하자
- 좋아, 체크
- 체크
-All right. Check.
-Check.
-I'm in for 50 cents.
-Call.
50센트 건다
받아
I'm in.
들어가
50센트 받고 5달러 더!
I see your 50 cents...
...and I raise you $5.
I thought it was a 50-cent limit.
50센트가 한계야
면접에서 미끄러졌는데
5달러도 못 올려?
I just lost a job,
I'd like to raise it $5.
Does anyone have
a problem with that?
여기 반대하는 사람?
-Not at all.
-No.
아냐, 해, 해
패배자님?
Loser?
난 빠져
-No, I fold.
-What do you mean, you fold?
빠지다니? 안돼
이게 뭐야?
일단 카드가 돌고 나면
우정은 기대하지 말라며?
I thought that, "Once the cards
are dealt, I'm not a nice guy."
그건 허풍이었어?
Were you just full of it?
들어간다!
I'm in.
-How many do you want?
-One.
몇 장 줘?
한 장
Dealer takes two.
딜러는 두 장!
-What do you bet?
-I bet $2.
얼마나 걸 거야?
2달러
좋아, 2달러 받고...
Okay. I see your $2...
20달러 더
...and I raise you...
... 20.
I see your $20...
20달러 받고
25달러 더
... raise you $25.
25달러 받고...
모니카, 지갑 좀 봐줘
I see your $25
and Monica, get my purse.
Rachel, there's nothing in it.
레이첼, 비었어
그럼, 네 지갑 좀 봐
Okay, then get me your purse.
받아라, 행운을 빌어!
-Here you go. Good luck!
-Thank you.
고마워
25달러 받고, 7달러 더
I saw your $25 and I raise you...
...seven.
teen!
10달러
조이, 돈이 모자라
Joey, I'm a little shy.
왜 그래
나한테 부탁하는 거야?
That's okay, Ross. You can ask me.
-What do you need?
-1 5.
얼마야? 얼마?
- 그래, 여기 10
- 나도 5달러 있어
-Here's 10.
-I got 5.
- 고마워
- 행운을 빈다
-Thank you.
-Good luck.
17달러 받았어
네 패가 뭐야?
I am calling your 1 7.
What do you got?
풀 하우스!
Full house.
네가 이겼어
You got me.
-That's tough to beat.
-I thought we had it!
- 괜찮아, 굉장한 게임이었어
- 네가 이긴 줄 알았어
이길 패가 아니라면
끝까지 아닌 거야
When you don't have the cards,
you don't have the cards.
어쨌든 저렇게 좋아하잖아!
But look how happy she is.
-Airmail.
-Airplane. Airport. Airport '75!
- 비행기
- 항공 우편
공항 75, 공항 77, 공항 79
Airport '77! Airport '79!
Time's up!
시간 됐어
바이, 바이, 새!
Bye Bye Birdie!
그게 새야?
That's a bird?
새구나!
That's a bird!
Okay, it's my turn.
좋아, 내 차례야
가라!
Go!
콩, 콩!
Bean! Bean!
The Unbearable Lightness of Being!
참을 수 없는 존재의 가벼움!
맞아!
저걸 맞춰?
That you get?
That you get?!